Help on function st_folium in module streamlit_folium:

st_folium(fig: 'folium.MacroElement', key: 'str | None' = None, height: 'int' = 700, width: 'int | None' = 500, returned_objects: 'Iterable[str] | None' = None, zoom: 'int | None' = None, center: 'tuple[float, float] | None' = None, feature_group_to_add: 'list[folium.FeatureGroup] | folium.FeatureGroup | None' = None, return_on_hover: 'bool' = False, use_container_width: 'bool' = False, layer_control: 'folium.LayerControl | None' = None, pixelated: 'bool' = False, debug: 'bool' = False, render: 'bool' = True, on_change: 'Callable | None' = None, wrap_longitude: 'bool' = False)
    Display a Folium object in Streamlit, returning data as user interacts
    with app.
    Parameters
    ----------
    fig  : folium.Map or folium.Figure
        Geospatial visualization to render
    key: str or None
        An optional key that uniquely identifies this component. If this is
        None, and the component's arguments are changed, the component will
        be re-mounted in the Streamlit frontend and lose its current state.
    returned_objects: Iterable
        A list of folium objects (as keys of the returned dictionary) that will be
        returned to the user when they interact with the map. If None, all folium
        objects will be returned. This is mainly useful for when you only want your
        streamlit app to rerun under certain conditions, and not every time the user
        interacts with the map. If an object not in returned_objects changes on the map,
        the app will not rerun.
    zoom: int or None
        The zoom level of the map. If None, the zoom level will be set to the
        default zoom level of the map. NOTE that if this zoom level is changed, it
        will *not* reload the map, but simply dynamically change the zoom level.
    center: tuple(float, float) or None
        The center of the map. If None, the center will be set to the default
        center of the map. NOTE that if this center is changed, it will *not* reload
        the map, but simply dynamically change the center.
    feature_group_to_add: List[folium.FeatureGroup] or folium.FeatureGroup or None
        If you want to dynamically add features to a feature group, you can pass
        the feature group here. NOTE that if you add a feature to the map, it
        will *not* reload the map, but simply dynamically add the feature.
    return_on_hover: bool
        If True, the app will rerun when the user hovers over the map, not
        just when they click on it. This is useful if you want to dynamically
        update your app based on where the user is hovering. NOTE: This may cause
        performance issues if the app is rerunning too often.
    use_container_width: bool
        If True, set the width of the map to the width of the current container.
        This overrides the `width` parameter.
    layer_control: folium.LayerControl or None
        If you want to have layer control for dynamically added layers, you can
        pass the layer control here.
    pixelated: bool
        If True, add CSS rules to render image crisp pixels which gives a pixelated
        result instead of a blurred image.
    debug: bool
        If True, print out the html and javascript code used to render the map with
        st.code
    render: bool
        If True, the map will be rendered as html, this must be done at least once.
        Disabling this may improve performance as you can cache the rendering step.
        *Note* if this is disabled and the map is not rendered elsewhere the map
        will be missing attributes
    wrap_longitude: bool
        If True, normalize longitude values to be within -180 to 180 degrees.
        This is useful when panning around the world causes longitude values to
        exceed the standard bounds.
    Returns
    -------
    dict
        Selected data from Folium/leaflet.js interactions in browser

